<idea-plugin>
  <id>cn.haloop.swi.openapi</id>
  <name>Swi OpenAPI</name>
  <vendor email="mawh@bxlsj.com" url="https://www.haloop.cn">StarWish Tech</vendor>
  <description>
    <![CDATA[
    <h2>Swi OpenAPI - Seamless API Documentation for Go Projects</h2>

    <p>Swi OpenAPI is an IntelliJ plugin specifically designed for Go developers using the Gin Web framework. It streamlines the process of creating and maintaining API documentation by automatically generating Apifox JSON Schema documentation directly from your Go code. This plugin eliminates the need for Swagger or other API frameworks, offering a lightweight and integrated solution for API documentation.</p>

    <h3>Key Features:</h3>
    <ul>
        <li><strong>Automatic Documentation:</strong> Effortlessly generate comprehensive Apifox JSON Schema API documentation from your Go source code.</li>
        <li><strong>Gin Framework Integration:</strong> Specially tailored for projects using the Gin Web framework, ensuring accurate documentation that aligns with your code structure.</li>
        <li><strong>Easy Documentation Management:</strong> Manage and view your API documentation within the IntelliJ environment, staying within your development workflow.</li>
        <li><strong>Real-time Updates:</strong> Documentation updates automatically with code changes, keeping documentation consistent with the latest codebase.</li>
        <li><strong>User-friendly:</strong> Simple installation with no additional dependencies, designed for a smooth and efficient development experience.</li>
    </ul>

    <p>Swi OpenAPI is perfect for Go developers seeking to enhance their API documentation process, ensuring accuracy, ease of use, and integration with their existing Go projects.</p>

    <h2>Swi OpenAPI - 无缝集成的API文档生成工具</h2>

    <p>Swi OpenAPI 是一个为 Go 语言开发者设计的 IntelliJ 插件，旨在解决在 Go 项目中创建和维护 API 文档的挑战。这个插件特别适用于使用 Gin Web 框架的 Go 项目，提供了一种无需依赖 Swagger 或其他 API 框架的方法来自动生成 API 文档。</p>

    <h3>主要特点：</h3>
    <ul>
        <li><strong>自动生成 API 文档：</strong>通过分析您的 Go 代码，这个插件能够自动生成 ApiFox JSON Schema 格式的 API 文档，极大地简化了文档的创建和更新过程。</li>
        <li><strong>对 Gin 框架的深度支持：</strong>本插件专为 Gin Web 框架量身定做，能够无缝集成并识别 Gin 的路由和控制器结构，确保文档的准确性和完整性。</li>
        <li><strong>便捷的文档管理：</strong>在 IntelliJ 环境中直接管理和浏览 API 文档，无需离开开发环境即可查看和更新文档。</li>
        <li><strong>易于维护和更新：</strong>随着代码的变更，API 文档会自动更新，确保文档始终与最新的代码保持一致。</li>
        <li><strong>轻量级且易于使用：</strong>不需要额外的依赖或复杂的配置，一键安装即可使用，为 Go 语言开发者带来极大的便利。</li>
    </ul>
    ]]>
  </description>
  <version>1.2.3</version>

<!--  <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>-->
  <depends>org.jetbrains.plugins.go</depends>
  <depends>com.intellij.modules.json</depends>

  <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
    <codeInsight.lineMarkerProvider
      language="go"
      implementationClass="cn.haloop.swi.openapi.provider.SwiLineMarkerProvider"/>
  </extensions>
  <actions>
  </actions>
</idea-plugin>